Mark Winston fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Consulting records, 1981 - 2010; F-174-6; 55.7 cm of textual records 3 videocassettes; Physical description: includes 3 VHS videocassettes and 3 digital access copies.
  - Dialogue and facilitation, 2002 - 2009; F-174-6-2; 35.3 cm of textual records
    - Action Canada Vancouver 2006/2007 - working conference, F-174-6-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 174-86)
    - Action Canada - Toronto/Ottawa 2006-2007 - working conference, F-174-6-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 174-86)
    - Action Canada Alberta 2007 - working conference, F-174-6-2-0-15 (Archival box - standard 174-86)
    - Action Canada op-ed 2006 - 2007, 2006 - 2008; F-174-6-2-0-16 (Archival box - standard 174-86)
    - Action Canada 2005/2006: general and Ottawa Dialogue session, F-174-6-2-0-17 (Archival box - standard 174-86)
    - Action Canada: selection 2005, F-174-6-2-0-18 (Archival box - standard 174-87)
    - Action Canada 2005/2006: Fellows, F-174-6-2-0-19 (Archival box - standard 174-87)
    - Action Canada 2005: Fellows' writing, 2005 - 2007; F-174-6-2-0-20 (Archival box - standard 174-87)
    - Action Canada 2005/2006: Vancouver conference, F-174-6-2-0-21 (Archival box - standard 174-87)
    - Action Canada 2005/2006: Ottawa conference, F-174-6-2-0-22 (Archival box - standard 174-87)
    - Action Canada: 2004 selection, 2003 - 2004; F-174-6-2-0-23 (Archival box - standard 174-87)
    - Action Canada Fellows 2004/2005, F-174-6-2-0-24 (Archival box - standard 174-87)
    - Action Canada 2004/2005 Generations - group project, 2004 - 2007; F-174-6-2-0-25 (Archival box - standard 174-87)
    - Action Canada: 2004-2005 conferences, F-174-6-2-0-26 (Archival box - standard 174-87)
    - Action Canada Vancouver conference 2004/2005, F-174-6-2-0-27 (Archival box - standard 174-87)
    - Action Canada Ottawa conference 2004/2005, F-174-6-2-0-28 (Archival box - standard 174-87)
    - Action Canada Yukon conference 2004/2005, F-174-6-2-0-29 (Archival box - standard 174-87)
    - Action Canada/final report/2004, F-174-6-2-0-30 (Archival box - standard 174-87)
    - Action Canada: 2003-2004 Fellows, vol. 1, 2003 - 2006; F-174-6-2-0-31 (Archival box - standard 174-88)
    - Action Canada: 2003-2004 Fellows, vol. 2, 2003 - 2006; F-174-6-2-0-32 (Archival box - standard 174-88)
    - Action Canada: Newfoundland conference, 2004; F-174-6-2-0-33 (Archival box - standard 174-88)
- Apimondia '99 Conference, 1991 - 2000; F-174-7; 58.1 cm of textual records 78 photographs 108 photographs: col. slides 3 souvenir pins; Physical description: photographs include 20 slides (file 42) and 58 digital photographs in the form of a pdf (file 43).
  Series consists of records relating to Mark Winston's role as Program Chair for the Apimondia '99 conference held in Vancouver, BC in 1999 and includes correspondence with the Organizing Committee, presenters, vendors, and conference and hotel venues; promotion and local news publicity announcements; contracts and budget papers; volunteer supervision; and conference program packages.
  Records include correspondence, working papers, reports, minutes, conference proceedings, publications, slides, photographs, and promotional materials.
  Textual records; Photographic materials; Artefacts
  - Hosting bid, 1991 - 1995; F-174-7-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 174-51)
  - Logo, 1995 - 1997; F-174-7-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 174-51)
  - Hotel, 1995 - 1999; F-174-7-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 174-51)
  - Promotion and publicity, 1995 - 1999; F-174-7-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 174-51)
  - Program, vol. 1, 1995 - 1999; F-174-7-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 174-51)
  - Program, vol. 2, 1995 - 1999; F-174-7-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 174-51)
  - Agreements, 1995 - 1999; F-174-7-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 174-51)
  - Funding, 1995 - 2000; F-174-7-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 174-51)
  - Organizing Committee, vol. 1, 1995 - 2000; F-174-7-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 174-51)
  - Organizing Committee, vol. 2, 1995 - 2000; F-174-7-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 174-52)
  - Tours, 1996 - 1999; F-174-7-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 174-52)
  - Program: Pathology, 1996 - 1999; F-174-7-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 174-52)
  - Sponsors, 1996 - 1999; F-174-7-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 174-52)
  - Program: Economy, vol. 1, 1996 - 1999; F-174-7-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 174-52)
  - Program: Economy, vol. 2, 1996 - 1999; F-174-7-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 174-52)
  - VISA requirements, 1997; F-174-7-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 174-52)
  - Support, 1997; F-174-7-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 174-52)
  - Souvenirs, 1997 - 1999; F-174-7-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 174-52)
  - Media, 1997 - 1999; F-174-7-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 174-52)
  - Program: no category, 1997 - 1999; F-174-7-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 174-53)
  - Program: Technology and equipment, 1997 - 1999; F-174-7-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 174-53)
  - Program: Rural development, 1997 - 1999; F-174-7-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 174-53)
  - Audio-visual, 1997 - 1999; F-174-7-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 174-53)
  - Proceedings, 1997 - 1999; F-174-7-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 174-53)
  - Unsuccessful bids, 1997 - 1999; F-174-7-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 174-53)
  - Convention Centre, 1997 - 1999; F-174-7-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 174-53)
  - Program: Biology, 1997 - 1999; F-174-7-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 174-53)
  - Program: Melliferous, vol. 1, 1997 - 1999; F-174-7-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 174-54)
  - Program: Melliferous, vol. 2, 1997 - 1999; F-174-7-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 174-54)
  - Canada Post stamp, 1998; F-174-7-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 174-54)
  - Program: Apitherapy, 1998 - 1999; F-174-7-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 174-54)
  - 1 and 2 circular, 1998 - 1999; F-174-7-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 174-54)
  - Api Expo, 1998 - 1999; F-174-7-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 174-54)
  - Volunteers, 1998 - 1999; F-174-7-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 174-54)
  - Translation, 1998 - 1999; F-174-7-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 174-54)
  - Keynote speech, 1999; F-174-7-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 174-54)
  - Souvenir program, 1999; F-174-7-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 174-54)
  - Photography/video, 1999; F-174-7-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 174-54)
  - Conference publications, 1999; F-174-7-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 174-54)
  - Program: submitted papers, 1999; F-174-7-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 174-54)
  - Proceedings - bound copy, 1999; F-174-7-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 174-54)
  - Conference sponsors (slides), 1999; F-174-7-0-0-42 (Archival box - small 174-63)
  - Apimondia '99 photographs (CD), 1999; F-174-7-0-0-43 (Optical disc: cd OBJ-1071)
    Includes 1 pdf file slideshow of 58 images.
  - Apimondia '99 Event Book, 1999; F-174-7-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 174-55)
  - Apimondia '99 Event Book, 1999; F-174-7-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 174-55)
  - Apimondia '99 promotional slide set, 1999; F-174-7-0-0-46; 20 photographs: col. slides (Archival box - small 174-99)
  - Beekeeping in the New Millennium; Swarming; Behaviour:..., 1999; F-174-7-0-0-47; 88 photographs: col. slides (Archival box - small 174-99)
  - Apimondia items, 1999 - 2000; F-174-7-0-0-48; Includes 1 photograph and 3 souvenir pins (Archival box - standard 174-88)
    Photographic materials; Textual records; Artefacts
- Professional organizations, 1981 - 2009; F-174-8; 81.4 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to Mark Winston's correspondence with, and participation on, local, national and international apiculture and other organizations. Records include correspondence, working papers, agendas, minutes, reports, grant applications, newsletters and publications.
  Series is arranged into 13 sub-series:
  1. Biocontrol Network External Advisory Board
  2. BC Honey Producers Association (BCHPA)
  3. BC Pollination Working Group
  4. Canadian Association of Professional Apiculturists (CAPA)
  5. Canadian Bees Research Foundation (CBRF)
  6. International Bee Research Association (IBRA)
  7. International Union for the Study of Social Insects (IUSSI)
  8. Pacific National Exhibition Apiculture Committee
  9. Pollen Bee Foundation Inc.
  10. Professional Pest Management Association of BC (PPMA)
  11. Western Apiculture Society (WAS)
  12. Friends of the Environment
  13. Other organizations
  Files in this series that marked 'pending review' must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release, and as a result of the review, access restrictions may apply. Please see the file list for this series and consult the archivist for more details.
  - Biocontrol Network External Advisory Board, 2002 - 2005; F-174-8-1; 2 cm of textual records
    Biocontrol Network External Advisory Board
    - Biocontrol, 2002 - 2005; F-174-8-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 174-55)
  - BC Honey Producers Association (BCHPA), 1981 - 1995; F-174-8-2; 6 cm of textual records
    British Columbia Honey Producers Association
    - Education Committee, vol. 1, 1981 - 1994; F-174-8-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 174-55)
    - Education Committee, vol. 2, 1981 - 1994; F-174-8-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 174-55)
    - Newsletters, research reviews, reports, 1981 - 1995; F-174-8-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 174-55)
  - BC Pollination Working Group, 1984 - 1985; F-174-8-3; 2 cm of textual records
    British Columbia Pollination Working Group
    - Correspondence, 1984 - 1985; F-174-8-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 174-56)
  - Canadian Association of Professional Apiculturists (CAPA), 1985 - 2000; F-174-8-4; 40 cm of textual records
    - Importation and mites, vol. 1, 1985 - 1995; F-174-8-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 174-56)
    - Importation and mites, vol. 2, 1985 - 1995; F-174-8-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 174-56)
    - Importation and mites, vol. 3, 1985 - 1995; F-174-8-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 174-56)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1987 - 1997; F-174-8-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 174-56)
    - Research meeting, 1989 - 1990; F-174-8-4-0-5 (Archival box - standard 174-56)
    - Killer Bees press releases, 1990 - 1994; F-174-8-4-0-6 (Archival box - standard 174-56)
    - Research Committee, 1990 - 1997; F-174-8-4-0-7 (Archival box - standard 174-56)
    - Pollination, 1990 - 1997; F-174-8-4-0-8 (Archival box - standard 174-57)
    - CAPA/CHC FSAM research projects, vol. 1, 1992; F-174-8-4-0-9 (Archival box - standard 174-57)
    - CAPA/CHC FSAM research projects, vol. 2, 1992; F-174-8-4-0-10 (Archival box - standard 174-57)
    - FSAM II funding, vol. 1, 1992 - 1995; F-174-8-4-0-11 (Archival box - standard 174-57)
    - FSAM II funding, vol. 2, 1992 - 1995; F-174-8-4-0-12 (Archival box - standard 174-57)
    - Annual meeting, 1993 - 1995; F-174-8-4-0-13 (Archival box - standard 174-57)
    - Newsletter, 1993 - 1996; F-174-8-4-0-14 (Archival box - standard 174-57)
    - Mayer response, 1993; F-174-8-4-0-15 (Archival box - standard 174-58)
    - Apiary Inspectors of America correspondence, 1994; F-174-8-4-0-16 (Archival box - standard 174-58)
    - Importations - Bumble Bees, 1994; F-174-8-4-0-17 (Archival box - standard 174-58)
    - OIE report, 1994 - 1995; F-174-8-4-0-18 (Archival box - standard 174-58)
    - Correspondence, 1994 - 1995; F-174-8-4-0-19 (Archival box - standard 174-58)
    - Canadian Honey Council Symposium, 1994 - 1995; F-174-8-4-0-20 (Archival box - standard 174-58)
    - Check-off, 1994 - 1996; F-174-8-4-0-21 (Archival box - standard 174-58)
    - Chemical Committee, 1994 - 1997; F-174-8-4-0-22 (Archival box - standard 174-58)
    - CAPA/CHC meeting, 1995; F-174-8-4-0-23 (Archival box - standard 174-58)
    - Research meeting, 1995 - 1996; F-174-8-4-0-24 (Archival box - standard 174-58)
    - World Trade/import, 1996; F-174-8-4-0-25 (Archival box - standard 174-58)
    - CAPA/CHC meeting, 1996 - 1997; F-174-8-4-0-26 (Archival box - standard 174-58)
    - Research fund, vol. 1, 1996 - 2000; F-174-8-4-0-27 (Archival box - standard 174-59)
    - Research fund, vol. 2, 1996 - 2000; F-174-8-4-0-28 (Archival box - standard 174-59)
    - CAPA/CHC meeting, 1997; F-174-8-4-0-29 (Archival box - standard 174-59)
  - Canadian Bees Research Foundation (CBRF), 1997 - 2000; F-174-8-5; 6 cm of textual records
    Canadian Bees Research Foundation
    - Correspondence and grant applications, 1997 - 1998; F-174-8-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 174-59)
    - Grant competitions, vol. 1, 1997 - 2000; F-174-8-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 174-59)
    - Grant competitions, vol. 2, 1997 - 2000; F-174-8-5-0-3 (Archival box - standard 174-59)
    - Correspondence and grant applications, 1999 - 2000; F-174-8-5-0-4 (Archival box - standard 174-59)
  - International Bee Research Association (IBRA), 1985 - 1988; F-174-8-6; 1 cm of textual records
    International Bee Research Association
    - Correspondence, 1985 - 1988; F-174-8-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 174-59)
  - International Union for the Study of Social Insects (IUSSI), 1984 - 1999; F-174-8-7; 4 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence and working papers, 1984 - 1988; F-174-8-7-0-1 (Archival box - standard 174-59)
    - Correspondence and working papers, 1993 - 1998; F-174-8-7-0-2 (Archival box - standard 174-60)
    - IUSSI Australia, 1995 - 1999; F-174-8-7-0-3 (Archival box - standard 174-60)
  - Pacific National Exhibition Apiculture Committee, 1990 - 1991; F-174-8-8; 1 cm of textual records
    Pacific National Exhibition Apiculture Committee
    - Correspondence, working papers and reports, 1990 - 1991; F-174-8-8-0-1 (Archival box - standard 174-60)
  - Pollen Bee Foundation Inc., 1999 - 2001; F-174-8-9; 1 cm of textual records
    Pollen Bee Foundation Inc.
    - Correspondence and reports, 1999 - 2001; F-174-8-9-0-1 (Archival box - standard 174-60)
  - Professional Pest Management Association of BC (PPMA), 1997 - 1998; F-174-8-10; 1 cm of textual records
    Professional Pest Management Association of BC
    - Correspondence and reports, 1997 - 1998; F-174-8-10-0-1 (Archival box - standard 174-60)
  - Western Apiculture Society (WAS), 1984 - 1994; F-174-8-11; 6 cm of textual records
    - Conference Committee, 1984 - 1986; F-174-8-11-0-1 (Archival box - standard 174-60)
    - Correspondence and working papers, 1985 - 1986; F-174-8-11-0-2 (Archival box - standard 174-60)
    - Correspondence, working papers and reports, vol. 1, 1992 - 1994; F-174-8-11-0-3 (Archival box - standard 174-60)
    - Correspondence, working papers and reports, vol. 1, 1992 - 1994; F-174-8-11-0-4 (Archival box - standard 174-60)
  - Friends of the Environment, 2003 - 2006; F-174-8-12; 2 cm of textual records
    Friends of the Environment
    - Correspondence and working papers, 2003 - 2006; F-174-8-12-0-1 (Archival box - standard 174-73)
      Friends of the Environment; Textual records
  - Other organizations, 2004 - 2009; F-174-8-13; 8.4 cm of textual records
    - Jack Webster Awards - science and technology jury member, 2005 - 2009; F-174-8-13-0-1 (Archival box - standard 174-88)
    - Vancouver Foundation: Education Committee, vol. 1, 2004 - 2009; F-174-8-13-0-2 (Archival box - standard 174-88)
    - Vancouver Foundation: Education Committee, vol. 2, 2004 - 2009; F-174-8-13-0-3 (Archival box - standard 174-89)
    - ICC Citizenship Ceremony Committee, 2008 - 2009; F-174-8-13-0-4 (Archival box - standard 174-89)
    - Liberal Party Renewal Commission, 2006; F-174-8-13-0-5 (Archival box - standard 174-89)
- Undergraduate Semester in Dialogue and Centre for Dialogue records, 2000 - 2014; F-174-9; 65.8 cm of textual records 3 photographs 2 optical discs
  Series consists of records documenting the establishment and development of SFU's Undergraduate Semester in Dialogue (USD) program by Mark Winston in his capacity as director of the program. It also includes records relating to the development of SFU's Centre for Dialogue and its programs by Winston in his capacity as the Centre's academic director and as a fellow. Records include correspondence, agendas, minutes, reports, proposals, photographs, and other materials.
  The series is arranged into 2 sub-series in order to keep separate the records of the USD program, which entail administrative records created and received by Winston in the course of his activities in founding, developing, and sustaining this academic program for the university. These materials are unique and considered university records. However, because Winston created and received these university records as he created and received his personal papers, the archivist opted to keep them in Winston's fonds rather than remove them to a university fonds.
  1. Undergraduate Semester in Dialogue program
  2. Centre for Dialogue
  Textual records; Photographic materials; Sound recordings; Multi-media
  Files in this series contain university records, which are subject to BC's Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act [RSBC 1996] Chapter 165. All files marked 'pending review' must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release. As a result of the review, access restrictions may apply. Please see the file list for this series and consult the archivist for more details.
  - Undergraduate Semester in Dialogue program, 2000 - 2014; F-174-9-1; 40.6 cm of textual records 3 photographs 1 optical disc; Semester in Dialogue
    Sub-series consists of records documenting the establishment and development of SFU's Undergraduate Semester in Dialogue (USD) program by Mark Winston in his capacity as director of the program. Since the records are originals and were created and received by Winston in the course of his activities in founding, developing, and sustaining this academic program for the university, they are considered official university records. Records include correspondence, agendas, minutes, reports, proposals, budgets, and photographs.
    Textual records; Photographic materials; Sound recordings
    Files in this sub-series contain university records, which are subject to BC's Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act [RSBC 1996] Chapter 165. All files marked 'pending review' must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release. As a result of the review, access restrictions may apply. Please see the file list for this sub-series and consult the archivist for more details.
    - Fundraising general, 2001 - 2003; F-174-9-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 174-89)
    - Carthy Foundation, 2002 - 2005; F-174-9-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 174-89)
    - McConnell Foundation, 2001 - 2004; F-174-9-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 174-89)
    - McConnell Foundation 2004, 2003 - 2005; F-174-9-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 174-89)
    - Learning for a Sustainable Future - SFU Working Group for Sustainability Education initiative, 2006; F-174-9-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 174-89)
    - Adaptations to Climate Change - ACT Team/Steering Committee, 2006 - 2009; F-174-9-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 174-89)
    - Advertising 2004/2005, 2003 - 2004; F-174-9-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 174-90)
    - Advertising 2003-3 - Urban Experience course, 2002 - 2004; F-174-9-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 174-90)
    - Nature/Environment: advertising, 2001 - 2002; F-174-9-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 174-90)
    - Faculty workshops: dialogue - new faculty orientation program, 2005 - 2010; F-174-9-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 174-90)
    - Inquiries, vol. 1, 2003 - 2008; F-174-9-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 174-90)
    - Inquiries, vol. 2, 2003 - 2008; F-174-9-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 174-90)
    - Dialogue minor - School of Communication proposal, 2004 - 2005; F-174-9-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 174-90)
    - Cathie Dunlop: evaluation of program, 2002 - 2003; F-174-9-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 174-90)
    - Blizzard Award, 2005 - 2008; F-174-9-1-0-15 (Archival box - standard 174-90)
    - Proposals: Faculty, 2003 - 2006; F-174-9-1-0-16 (Archival box - standard 174-91)
    - Peace and Security - topic proposal, 2003 - 2004; F-174-9-1-0-17 (Archival box - standard 174-91)
    - Citizenship - call for Faculty proposals, 2006 - 2008; F-174-9-1-0-18 (Archival box - standard 174-91)
    - Olympics - program topic, 2005 - 2007; F-174-9-1-0-19 (Archival box - standard 174-91)
      Textual records; Sound recordings
      - Contrapuntal Dialogue: An Audio Documentary of A 2010-Piece Puzzle, 2007; F-174-9-1-0-19-1; 1 optical disc (CD-R) (Optical disc: cd OBJ-4913)
        Catalano, Cameron; Sound recordings; Textual records
    - Being About Action: Local Leaders, Global Futures (2006-2) - program topic, F-174-9-1-0-20 (Archival box - standard 174-91)
    - Early days Wosk Centre for Dialogue and Undergraduate Semester in Dialogue, 2001 - 2007; F-174-9-1-0-21; Includes 3 photographs (Archival box - standard 174-91)
    - USD proposal, 2001 - 2002; F-174-9-1-0-22 (Archival box - standard 174-91)
    - Senate Committee on Undergraduate Studies, 2001 - 2002; F-174-9-1-0-23 (Archival box - standard 174-91)
    - USD next steps and reporting, 2002 - 2008; F-174-9-1-0-24 (Archival box - standard 174-91)
    - USD space/facilities, 2001 - 2012; F-174-9-1-0-25 (Archival box - standard 174-92)
    - USD and Centre for Dialogue budget/financial, 2001 - 2014; F-174-9-1-0-26 (Archival box - standard 174-92)
    - USD PR/media, 2001 - 2005; F-174-9-1-0-27 (Archival box - standard 174-92)
    - USD: registrar, 2002 - 2006; F-174-9-1-0-28 (Archival box - standard 174-92)
    - USD and Centre for Dialogue websites, 2002 - 2007; F-174-9-1-0-29 (Archival box - standard 174-92)
    - Associated centres for dialogue, 2004 - 2007; F-174-9-1-0-30 (Archival box - standard 174-92)
    - General course information - program creation, marketing, guidelines for teaching in, 2000 - 2009; F-174-9-1-0-31 (Archival box - standard 174-92)
  - Centre for Dialogue, 2002 - 2012; F-174-9-2; 25.2 cm of textual records 1 optical disc
    Sub-series consists of records relating to the development of SFU's Centre for Dialogue and its programs by Mark Winston in his capacity as the Centre's academic director and as a fellow. Unlike the USD program records, these materials are not considered official university records as they are not unique and are reflected in the records still held by the Centre itself. Records include correspondence, agendas, minutes, reports, proposals, and background literature.
    Textual records; Multi-media
    - SFU/Vancouver campus - general reference material, 2004 - 2005; F-174-9-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 174-92)
    - Public Servant in Residence, 2007 - 2008; F-174-9-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 174-92)
    - Tony Penikett - Centre for Dialogue Fellow book launch, 2006; F-174-9-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 174-92)
    - Sigurdson, Glenn - Fellow, 2006 - 2007; F-174-9-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 174-92)
    - Kristie Berg - PhD student interested in studying Centre, 2008; F-174-9-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 174-92)
    - Dialogue Associates, [2007?]; F-174-9-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 174-92)
    - North Dialogues - Imagine BC Advisory Committee, vol. 1, 2003 - 2010; F-174-9-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 174-93)
    - North Dialogues - Imagine BC Advisory Committee, vol. 2, 2003 - 2010; F-174-9-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 174-93)
      Textual records; Moving images
      - Health and Community in BC: Bowen Dialogue 2007, F-174-9-2-0-8-1; 1 optical disc (DVD) (Optical disc: dvd OBJ-4912)
        Continuing Studies; Moving images
    - Dialogue structure & plans 2006/2011, 2005 - 2011; F-174-9-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 174-93)
    - Dialogue group: plans, vol. 1, 2003 - 2009; F-174-9-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 174-93)
    - Dialogue group: plans, vol. 2, 2003 - 2009; F-174-9-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 174-93)
    - Centre for Dialogue Steering Committee, 2004 - 2010; F-174-9-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 174-93)